https://webtransitions.com/privacy-policy/

540-334-3831 sales@webtransitions.com
Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://webtransitions.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site or provide comments through the email contact service we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.CookiesWe use cookies to track your movement through the site. We do not sell or give any information collected through cookies with any one. If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withWe don’t share you data with anyone not specifically set out in this document.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Our contact informationWeb Transitions PO Box 638 Boones Mill, VA 24065 admin@webtransitions.com 540-334-1707How we protect your dataOur hosting environment and software is updated on a weekly basis. This includes the most current software, plugins and server software that is available. This software includes processes that monitor the server and site software for data hacking attempts and notifies us. This site does not collect any personal data.What data breach procedures we have in placeAll data services are turned off when we receive any data breach notification.What third parties we receive data fromNone.What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataNone.
Bits and Pieces
Search for:
Recent Posts Is your domain expiring? January 18, 2019 Customizing Your Web Mail Preferences January 14, 2019 Why host local? November 12, 2018 Effective Online Ad Campaigns November 10, 2018 Online Marketing November 10, 2018 CategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryEmail Support  (1)Stuff you should know  (4)
ArchivesJanuary 2019November 2018
